Guide to the Ralph R. Sundquist Papers 1909-1980
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 4. Civic Interests
  - 4.2 First Presbyterian Church of Yakima
    - The Windows of Heaven Were Opened, Windows of the First Presbyterian Church (Box 10, Folder 251)
    - The Yakima Presbyterian, various issues (Box 10, Folder 252)
  - 4.3 Yakima Public Schools
    - Board of Directors Reports, etc., part 1 (Box 11, Folder 253)
    - Board of Directors Reports, etc., part 2 (Box 11, Folder 254)
    - J. Roy Brown (Box 11, Folder 255)
    - Educational Television (Box 11, Folder 256)
    - Minutes, Board of Directors Meetings, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 257)
    - Minutes, Board of Directors Meetings, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 258)
    - Minutes, Board of Directors Meetings, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 259)
    - Minutes, Board of Directors Meetings, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 260)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 261)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 12, Folder 262)
    - Nob Hill Staff, correspondence, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 263)
    - Pamphlets and Programs (Box 12, Folder 264)
    - Photographs and Plans for Jr. and Sr. High Schools, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - Policies and By-Laws (Box 12, Folder 266)
    - Vocational Training (Box 12, Folder 267)
    - Yakima Public Schools, newsletter (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - 4.4 Yakima Public Schools Annual Reports, etc.
    - Annual Reports, Financial and Statistical, 6/30/1955 (Box 13, Folder 269)
    - Annual Reports, Financial and Statistical, 6/30/1958 (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - Final Budget, 1958-59 (Box 13, Folder 271)
    - Annual Reports, Financial and Statistical, 6/30/1959 (Box 13, Folder 272)
    - Accident Summary, 1959-60 (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Handbook for Substitute Teachers, Summer, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 274)
    - Library Handbook, Fall 1959 (Box 13, Folder 275)
    - Final Budget for 1959-60, 10/5/1959 (Box 13, Folder 276)
    - Annual Report on Curriculum, Jun-60 (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - Final Budget for 1960-61, 10/3/1960 (Box 13, Folder 278)
    - A Report on Evaluation of the Dwight D. Eisenhower Senior High School..., 11/1/1960 (Box 13, Folder 279)
    - Professional Growth Handbook for Teachers and Administrators, Nov-60 (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - Annual Reports, Financial and Statistical, 6/30/1960 (Box 13, Folder 281)
    - Report on Yakima School District No. 7, by Div. of Municipal Corporations, State of Wash, 5/22/1961 (Box 13, Folder 282)
    - Annual Reports, Financial and Statistical, 6/30/1961 (Box 13, Folder 283)
    - Annual Curriculum Report for 1960-61, Summer 1961 (Box 13, Folder 284)
    - Preliminary Budget for 1961-62 (Box 13, Folder 285)
    - Final Budget for 1961-62, 10/2/1961 (Box 13, Folder 286)
    - Annual Reports, Financial and Statistical, 6/30/1962 (Box 13, Folder 287)
    - Preliminary Budget for 1963-64, 4/8/1963 (Box 13, Folder 288)
    - Annual Reports, Financial and Statistical, 6/30/1963 (Box 13, Folder 289)
    - Final Budget for 1963-64, 10/7/1963 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - Building Survey, Feb-64 (Box 13, Folder 291)
    - Preliminary Budget for 1964-65, 4/2/1964 (Box 13, Folder 292)
    - Teachers' Responsibility in Controversial Issues, undated (Box 13, Folder 293)
  - 4.5 Yakima Valley College
    - Proposal to Establish an Associate Degree in Nursing, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - An Evaluation Report, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 295)
    - Self-Evaluation Report, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 296)
    - Preliminary Budget for 1963-64, 4/9/1963 (Box 14, Folder 297)
    - Final Budget for 1963-64, 10/7/1963 (Box 14, Folder 298)
    - Report of Self Study for Accreditation, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Harold A. Hoegland (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Misc. Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - Misc. Reports, Programs, etc (Box 14, Folder 302)
    - Misc. Reports, typed drafts (Box 14, Folder 303)
    - Newspaper clippings and newsprint annual reports (Box 14, Folder 304)
    - Newspaper, The Galaxy (Box 14, Folder 305)
    - Photographs, including images of Ralph Sundquist (Box 14, Folder 306)
    - Ralph Sundquist, recalling his long interest in the College (Box 14, Folder 307)
  - 4.6 Yakima Valley Memorial Hospital
    - Brochures, Pamphlets, Newsletters, 1950-1979 (Box 15, Folder 308)
    - Construction of Addition, newspaper clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 15, Folder 309)
    - Pledge Lists, Contributions for Construction, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 310)
    - Women's Auxiliary (Box 15, Folder 311)
  - 4.7 People to People Citizen Ambassador Program, World Tour, 1963
    - Ambassador-of-Good Will Certificate, Secretary of State, State of Washington (Box 15, Folder 312)
    - Guest List, American Embassy Residence, Rangoon, Burma (Box 15, Folder 313)
    - William McC. Martin, Jr., Federal Reserve Board (Box 15, Folder 314)
    - Catherine May, Member of Congress (Box 15, Folder 315)
    - Mobil Oil Turk A.S. (Box 15, Folder 316)
    - National Bank of Commerce (Box 15, Folder 317)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 15, Folder 318)
    - Newspaper Clippings, the Hurriyet, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 15, Folder 319)
    - Photographs of tour group (Box 15, Folder 320)
    - Program and Itinerary (Box 15, Folder 321)
    - Scandinavian Airlines System (SAS) (Box 15, Folder 322)
    - Visitor Passes, U.S. Senate, House, and Capitol; and People to People identity badge (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - 4.8 State College of Washington Degrees and Awards
    - Cadet Corps Warrant, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 324)
    - Certificate of Merit, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 325)
    - Diploma of Graduation, B.A. degree in Horticulture, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 326)
    - Diploma of Graduation, B.S. degree in Horticulture, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 327)
    - Diploma of Graduation, M.S. degree in Horticulture, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 328)
- Series 5. Sales Brochures for Farm Machinery, etc.
  - Allis-Chalmers Centrifugal Pumps (Box 16, Folder 329)
  - American Cyanamid Co., The Story of Cyanamid (Box 16, Folder 330)
  - Armco Iron, Coast Culvert and Flume Co, Portland (Box 16, Folder 331)
  - Best Pumps, Jones-Best Pump Mfg. Co., Seattle (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - Caterpillar Tractor (Box 16, Folder 333)
  - Cletrac Crawler Tractors, Cleveland Tractor Co. (Box 16, Folder 334)
  - John Deere Tractors, models A & B (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - DeLaval Centrifugal Pumps (Box 16, Folder 336)
  - Eisemann Types GS-4 & GS-4/2 Magnetos (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Fairbanks-Morse Horizontal Centrifugal Pumps (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Fordson Tractors (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - Friend Mfg. Co., sprayers (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Ganong Botanical Apparatus Catalogue (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Household Furnace fuel systems, oil blowers and coal stokers (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Interstate Clay Products Co., storage and ice houses (Box 16, Folder 343)
  - Killefer Implements, tillage equipment (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - McCormick-Deering Tractor Manure Spreader No. 200 (Box 16, Folder 345)
  - Moline Leverless Disc Harrow (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Moline Universal Tractor (Box 16, Folder 347)
  - Rumsey Triplex Power Pumps Catalog B-17 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Stark Bro's. Nurseries and Orchards Co. (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - United Iron Works Pumps (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - Ward's Invincible Triplex High Pressure Spray Pumps (Box 16, Folder 351)
  - Ward's National Science Establishment Catalogue (Box 16, Folder 352)
- Series 6. Oversize
  - A Memento, Class of 1916, Golden Grad Reunion, Photos Washington State University, May 27-29, 1966 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Our Yakima High, school song (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Debate Scoop, broad side, WSC, 1915 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - The Evergreen, 28-May-15 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Yakima Fruit Growers Association Grade and Packing Rules for Apples, 2 copies (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Who's Who on a portion of Yakima's Produce Row (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Thank you newspaper ad for participation in United Good Neighbors Campaign, Yakima Republic, includes cartoon likeness of Ralph Sundquist, 6-9-1964 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Jewish Morning Journal ad for Wash. Apples, in Hebrew (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Lower Naches Telephone Company line maps, two sheets (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Tabulation of Bids on addition to Yakima Valey Jr. College (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Tabulation of Bids on construction of Whitney Elem. School (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Site Plan Elevation, A. C. Davis Sr. High School, 1/4/1965 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Plot Plan, Hospital Building, Yakima, 11/13/1948 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Unit Two Floor Plan, Yakima Valley Jr. College, 8/1/1960 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Trust Account Cost/Profit ledger, two sheets, 1957 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Power Farming magazine, with article by Ralph Sundquist, April 1, 1920 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)
  - Anniversary Edition, Yakima Valley News Souvenir Pictorial, 1885-1960 (Box Oversize, Folder 353)